

NGO THI PHUONG NHI

BIM ENGINEER

CONTACT

16/04/2001

**** 0822 605 687

™ ntpnhi1604@gmail.com

District 8, Ho Chi Minh City

ntpnhi1604.github.io/portfolio-BIMEngineer/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

BIM SOFTWARE

Revit (Advanced)AutoCad (Intermediate)Dynamo (Beginner)

RENDER

Enscape (Intermediate)Twinmotion (Intermediate)

MICROSOFT OFFICE

Word (Advanced)
Excel (Intermediate)
PowerPoint (Intermediate)

SOFT SKILLS

- Attention to Detail
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- · Problem Solving

CERTIFICATES

• TOEIC L&R: 615

Revit Structure
 Issued by REACTEC - Ho Chi
 Minh City University of
 Technology (HCMUT)

ABOUT ME

I'm a BIM Modeler with 2 years of experience. I have contributed to over 6 projects spanning all phases of BIM, including Design, Shop Drawing, Fabrication, As-Built, and Operation & Maintenance.

Driven by a strong desire to learn and a high sense of responsibility, I am eager to find a working environment where I can develop my skills and contribute valuable assets to the company.

(The attached Portfolio Website provides detailed information about my work experience and the projects I have completed. Due to confidentiality, this CV focuses only on my overall skills and roles.)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Building Innovation Management Technology 05/2023 - Present Joint Stock Company (BIMTech JSC)

BIM ENGINEER

- Update and modify models in line with the latest design;
- · Perspective rendering;
- Implement Shop drawings of reinforced concrete structure;
- · Schedule, Update and Coordinate with site coordinating;
- Control, Report and Resolve conflicts;
- Build 3D interior models at LOD400 detail;
- Implement detail drawings for interior models.

BIMLAB - Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology (HCMUT)

05/2022 - 05/2023

INTERN

- · Implement finish drawings;
- Schedule, Update and Coordinate with site coordinating;
- Control, Report and Resolve conflicts;
- Update 3D models at LOD500 detail;
- Update non-geometric information for the model conforming to project standards.

EDUCATION

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology (HCMUT)

2019 - 2024

Bachelor of Civil and Industrial Engineering

- My Capstone Project was awarded a mark of 8.7, which was the highest distinction conferred that semester.
- Degree grade: Good GPA: 7.28 (Out of 10)

